Mss.Rec.94 Mss.Rec.94
American Philosophical Society
Musquakie Texts
1968
Mss.Rec.94
American Philosophical Society
9.0 Reel(s)
Unidentified, untranslated texts given in Meskwaki, also known as Fox. Recorded in Tama, Iowa between June and December 1968.
9 sound tape reels (2 hr., 1 min.): analog, 3 3/4 ips, 2 track, mono; 5 in.
Voorhis, Paul H.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Paul Voorhis in 1972 (Acc. 1972 2109rec). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
General note
Recording has some occassional background distortion due to power generator, miscellaneous ambient noises, and occasional line hum.
Related Archival Materials note
Project report available in Phillips Fund collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Fox language; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:03; Voorhis, Paul H.
    Scope and Contents note
    Speaker not identified in documentation.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Sound tape reel) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Fox language; Tama (Iowa)
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:04:12; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:02:06; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:52; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:18:49; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:24:15; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 07-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:12:00; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 08-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:18:57; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 08-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:18:24; Voorhis, Paul H.
  - Mesquakie Texts, 1968; 09-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:07:23; Voorhis, Paul H.